WKCC AM廣播電台 全天候為您服務
WKCC AM Talk Radio. All talk, all the time.
五點鐘將為您帶來體育和天氣消息
Bringing you sports and weather on the five.
教會領袖譴責報復以及種族攻擊...
Church leaders blame the rise of hate crimes and racially-motivated attacks...
...自稱"Holnists"的民兵組織
...on a militia-like group calling themselves ''The Holnists. ''
這些組織中最激進最強大的一個...
One of the most radical and powerful of these groups...
...它的創始人著名的Nathan Holn發表聲明
...claims as its founder, the famed motivational speaker Nathan Holn.
最後一個偉大的城市也消失了...
The last of the great cities died...
...在我父親還是個孩子的時候...
...when my father was a child...
...也是另一場戰爭的犧牲品
...victims of yet another war.
他講述了接下來的苦難歷程...
He told of the plagues that followed...
...散落在各個小村落裡的人們如何為了生存的希望...
...and how the living hid themselves, scattered in tiny hamlets...
...而互相殘殺...
...in hopes of surviving whatever new madness...
...陰謀掠奪倖存的壯丁
...conspired to rob them of the little that remained.
在那些日子裡，他一個人前行...
In those days, he walked alone...
...是那個混亂時代的孤獨見證者
...a solitary witness to the chaos that reigned.
地球本身也已經殘破不堪
The earth itself had fallen victim to the insanity.
他說有個冬天持續了三年...
He told stories of the 3-year winter...
...而髒雪卻又不停的下
...and how the dirty snow never stopped falling.
他還看見了海洋 不孕、中毒、就快要死了
He saw the ocean, barren, poisoned, near death.
而人們就仰望蒼穹16年...
And how they watched the sky for 1 6 long years...
...祈求這個偉大的地球的肺能夠重新開始運轉
...praying for the great lungs to start working again.
他說似乎海洋只能深深的一聲嘆息
He said it was as if the ocean had breathed a great sigh of relief.
許多來來往往的人們都放棄了他們的交通工具
Many commuters are abandoning their vehicles.
該死，Bill!
Goddamn it, Bill!
你知道我得先檢查一下的
You know l need to check it first.
我不知道
l don't know.
比松脂要好些
Better than turpentine, Bill.
味道也差不多
Tastes about the same.
你說呢？
What do you say?
你叫一聲阿
Your call.
你不會吹毛求疵的，Bill
You ain't picky, Bill.
我就喜歡你那樣
l like that about you.
就像我喜歡我的屁股
Things l like about my ass...
...第一:
...number 1 :
有松脂也不錯的
Will settle for turpentine.
我們找到個電視！
We got TV!
有147個頻道
We got 1 4 7 channels, Bill.
我們搞清楚從耶穌...
We got everything from...
...到危險的每件事
...Jesus to Jeopardy .
比如...
''Like...
...沙子穿過沙漏 日子也如此
...sands through the hourglass, so are the days--.''
我們會觀察的
We'll watch that.
...沙子穿過沙漏 日子也如此
...sands through the hourglass, so are the days of our lives.
"星期一"
''Monday.''
"星期一晚上"
''Monday night.''
星期一晚上足球
Monday-night football!
我可不想惹麻煩
l don't want any trouble.
我猜你也不想吧
l bet you don't either.
咱們和平解決吧
Let's just call it a draw.
我發財了
l'm rich!
我知道規則
l know the rule.
我的規則
lt's my rule.
不惜一切代價來避免文明
''Avoid civilization at all cost.''
我們得吃東西來，不是嗎？
We got to eat, don't we?
把嘴張開
Open your mouth.
我們是還沒有開始來做這些，但是...
lt's true we haven't done this for awhile but...
...看在上帝的份上 那就像是在騎自行車，Bill
...for God sakes, it's like riding a bicycle, Bill.
你有什麼好擔心的呢？
What are you so worried about?
你要做的不過是站在那裡
All you got to do is stand there.
一切都盡在我的掌握
l'm the one with all the lines.
張開
Open up.
說"Awful"
Awful.
說"awful"就行了
Just awful.
他們說「別害怕，Macbeth...
They said, ''Fear not, Macbeth...
...自從Birnam Wood...
...till Birnam Wood...
...來到了到Dunsinane」
...comes to Dunsinane.''
我說...
l said...
「...自從Birnam Wood 來到了Dunsinane!''
'' ...till Birnam Wood comes to Dunsinane!''
謝謝
Thank you.
拿起武器
Arm yourselves!
Arm yourselves.
如果巫婆的話沒錯...
lf the witch's words are true...
...它就不會跑，乖乖呆在這！
...there'll be no running, hiding here!
他們會反抗...
They'll fight...
...就如同我們最後一頓飯就靠它了
...as if our last meal depended on it.
明天....
Tomorrow....
And tomorrow....
明天
Tomorrow.
還有後天
And the day after that.
短小的蠟燭就將熄滅
Out, brief candle!
生命不過是個行走時的影子...
Life's but a walking shadow...
...一個可憐的演員...
...a poor player who struts...
...在舞台上消磨時光...
...and frets his hour upon a stage...
...再也聽不見
...and is heard no more.
這個故事的作者是....
lt's a tale told by....
ldiot.
一個低能兒...
A moron...
...只會大吵大鬧...
...full of sound and fury...
...其實...
...signifying...
...什麼也沒說
...nothing.
但是狂風啊，你刮吧
But blow, wind!
災難，你來吧
Come, wrack!
至少我們將會...
At least we'll die...
...戰士戰死沙場
...with the harness off our back!
我要和他談談
l want to talk to him.
孩子們以前從沒見過莎士比亞
The children have never seen Shakespeare before.
他們現在也還是沒見過阿
They still haven't.
謝謝你，你真是好人
Thank you. You're very kind.
我鼓掌是因為你身上發出臭味
l'm clapping because you stink.
Larry!
我想你還沒搞明白是怎麼一回事
l don't think you know how it works.
當我年輕時我也想當演員，不過一塌糊塗
When l was young, l tried to be an actor. l was awful.
但現在我不用擔心我是最差的了
But now l won't die thinking l was the worst one.
-別說了 -沒關係
-Stop it! -That's all right.
門票花了你多少錢？
How much did you pay to get in?
那就來咬我好了
So bite me.
你演的很好
You were very good.
-值不值得來點吃的？ -當然了，我們還有些湯
-Good enough to get something to eat? -Yes, we have some soup.
該死，是Holnists！
Holnists. Goddamn!
這些混蛋近來不殺人了
Bastards hardly kill anyone lately.
我們給他們些食物和物品
We give them food and supplies.
所有的鎮子都這麼做的
All the towns do.
我只是不想給他們我的任何東西
l'd just as soon not give them anything of mine, thanks.
你們在那裡幹嗎？
What are you doing there?
你們在幹嗎？
What are you doing?
這只是個遊戲，Bethlehem將軍
lt's just a game, General Bethlehem.
是他們在戲裡看到的一些東西 沒什麼傷害的
lt's something they saw in a play. No harm in it.
等等
Wait a minute!
一齣戲？
A play?
表演給我看看
Show me.
沒事的，孩子們，表演給我看看
lt's all right, children. Show me.
拿起武器
Arm yourselves.
不須跟著女巫跑
No running from the witches.
莎士比亞？
Shakespeare, is it?
真遺憾，我錯過了一齣好戲
l'm sorry l missed it.
我們幾乎沒有準備好我們想玩的遊戲
We haven't nearly stocked the game that we thought we would.
是嗎？ 但你們卻有時間演戲？
Really? But you had time for a play?
我要從每個鎮子...
l'm taking 3 conscripts...
...徵召三名士兵
...from each town!
他們將會很榮幸的為Holnist軍隊效勞...
They will have the honor of serving in the Holnist Army...
...直到我認為合適的時機為止
...until such time as l see fit!
3個男人
3 men.
能不能做到？
Could you do that?
隊長
Captain!
所有的男人...
All men...
...從15歲到50歲...
...between 1 5 and 50...
...有著適當的信仰基礎的 現在請自我展示
...and of suitable ethnic foundation are required to show themselves now!
將軍
General.
不用了，替我留著
No, but keep that.
接受
Acceptable.
長官？
Sir?
接受，隊長
Acceptable, Captain.
你得多吃肉，不過我欣賞你的頭腦
Need some meat on you, but l like an impressionable mind.
接受
Acceptable.
蒙古人
Mongoloid.
不要
Unacceptable.
我需要純種的
l want pure blood.
就像....
Someone....
-別揮手 -大家看著我
-Don't wave. -People, you will look at me!
就像....
Someone like....
就像那個人！
Like that man!
你誤會了
You don't understand.
你必須展示你自己
You were required to show yourself.
我不是他們一起的 我只是路過此地
l'm not with them. l'm just passing through.
把這傢伙帶走
Take the mule.
走，快走
Let's go! Move!
在這裡
Ten-hut!
呈一字形排開
l want a line right here.
先生們，歡迎開始你們的新生活
Welcome, gentlemen, to your new life.
你們在Nathan Holn聯軍裡獲得了新生
You have been born again as soldiers in the United Army of Nathan Holn.
上帝度假去了
God rest his soul!
強壯的男人們已經被...
The strong have been sapped...
...軟弱的哀號溶化了
...by the whimpering propaganda of the weak.
男人們...
Men...
...強壯的男人們 要反抗這種命運
...strong men, have been denied their destiny.
你們已經從那種命運中被解救了出來
You men have been saved from that fate.
贖金...
Redemption...
...就掌握在你們的手上
...is within your grasp.
你
You.
在獲得這個機會之前你是幹什麼的？
What did you do before you were given this opportunity?
我有把鐵鏟，我挖洞
l had a shovel. l digged holes.
你挖洞
You digged holes.
現在你得把洞都填滿了
Now you'll fill them.
你呢？
And you?
我？
Me?
你難道看不出來我是在和你說話嗎？
ls there any question in anyone's mind that l was speaking to you?
就是你
Yes, you.
我只是個演員
l'm just a performer.
比如莎士比亞的戲劇
Shakespeare. Stuff like that.
莎士比亞？
Shakespeare?
他是個作家
He was a writer.
這個我知道
Yes, l know.
我知道莎士比亞是誰
l know who Shakespeare was.
高喊著Havoc!...
''Cry 'Havoc!' ...
...讓戰爭帶來的傷害...
...and let slip...
...成為過去！
...the dogs of war.''
我？
Me?
「做還是不做
''To be or not to be:
著是個問題」
That is the question.''
「我們很少...
''We few...
...我們很少開心...
...we happy few...
...我們這幫兄弟們''
...we band of brothers!''
「現在通過約克之光，我們要...
''Now is the winter of our discontent made glorious summer...
...把不滿的冬天變成燦爛的夏天」
...by this sun of York.''
你相當不錯
You're pretty good.
你也是個鬥士 我可以從你的眼神裡看出來
You're also a fighter. l can see it in your eyes.
你是個危險人物
You are a dangerous man.
你不同意？
Don't you agree?
長官，我不是不尊敬你 不過你最好還是把我放了
No disrespect, sir, but you'd be better off letting me go.
把我逼上絕路我就是個鬥士
A fighter is about the last thing that l am.
難道你不認為這由我來決定嗎？
Don't you think l should be the judge of that, soldier?
起來
Get up.
我說起來
l said, get up!
你說的沒錯 你不是個鬥士
You're right. You're not a fighter.
但你將會成為一個鬥士
But you will be.
我給你個機會...
l'm giving you a chance at a life...
...讓你的生命有意義
...that means something.
值得好好過的生活
A life worth living.
-我很高興看到你們 -我們很想你
-I'm glad to see you. -We missed you.
-我也想你們，你還好嗎？ -我餓了
-I missed you. Kurt, how are you? -Hungry.
-Gretl,你的手指怎麼了？ -被抓過
-Gretl, what happened to your finger? -It got caught.
-被什麼抓過？ -Friedrich的牙齒
-Caught in what? -Friedrich's teeth.
謝謝
Thanks.
我贏了嗎？
Did l win?
我想要告訴他
l tried to tell him.
再說一遍
Say it again.
說什麼？
Say what?
你在鎮上說的那些話
Words you said in town.
關於颳風還有其它 再說一遍
About the wind blowing and the rest. Say it again.
狂風你刮吧 災難你來吧
''Blow, wind. Come, wrack.
至少我們將會戰士戰死沙場
At least we'll die with the harness off our back.''
那是什麼意思？
What's it mean?
要麼自由的活著
''Live free or...
要麼死去
...die.''
我想
l think.
你們要麼看電影要麼就睡覺
You're going to watch a movie or you can sleep!
但是明天...
But tomorrow...
...你們要穿上制服...
...you run in uniform...
...背滿包裹...
...full packs...
...跑20里路
...20 miles!
每個人都得做到...
Everybody makes it...
...否則大家都沒得吃...
...or nobody eats...
...第三天排成隊
...for the third day in a row!
大家都起來
Everybody up.
晚上有飯吃
You got meat tonight.
你為什麼不告訴莎士比亞它有多和藹？
Why don't you tell Shakespeare what kind it is?
騾子
Mule.
該死的動物
God-awful animal.
馬和驢子雜交的東西
Sterile offspring of horse and donkey.
你能想像嗎？
Can you imagine that?
在這個新世界裡，沒有那種混蛋的空間
There's no room in the New World for a bastard like that.
排在最後面的人肯定是還不很餓 所以沒有吃的
Any man last in line ain't hungry enough to eat.
你排在最後面...
You show up last...
...所以你沒得吃
...you don't eat!
我要是還排在最後一個我就去死
l'm going to die before l'm last in line again!
他們求之不得呢
That's what they're hoping for.
閉嘴！至少你還在吃！
Shut up! At least you're eating!
你當真？
You serious?
不錯
Good.
真不錯
This is good!
你想要這個？！
You want this?!
這就是你想要的？
This is what you want?
孩子們！
Babies!
這些山，因為有了音樂
The hills are alive
而充滿了生機
With the sound of music
這將會是我生命中最美好的年月
These were supposed to be the best years of my life.
先生們，八大法律
The Laws of Eight, gentlemen.
那是由Nathan Holn傳下來的遺產
That is the legacy handed down to us by Nathan Holn.
將永世長存
May he burn in hell.
這些是我們賴以生存的法寶
These are the laws that we live by.
8...
The 8...
...就是我們的象徵
...is our symbol.
每個人都將自豪的遵守
Each man will bear it with pride.
那樣你們才能成為我們幫派的一員
Only then will you be part of the clan.
先生們，請坐
Sit down, gentlemen.
第一條：
Law One:
你們必須無條件的服從命令 我叫你們坐下
You will obey orders without question. l told you to sit.
椅子不夠
There weren't enough chairs.
我沒說一定要坐椅子，你們可以坐在地上
l didn't specify chairs. You could've sat on the ground.
你們不執行一個明確的命令...
You disobeyed a direct order. You broke...
...你們違背了第一條
...Law One.
第二條：
Law Two:
懲罰會很迅速
Punishment shall be swift.
第三條
Law Three:
仁慈...
Mercy...
...是給弱者的
...is for the weak.
第四條：
Four:
恐怖...
Terror...
...必將戰勝理性
...will defeat reason.
第五條
Five:
你們要效忠幫派
Your allegiance is to the clan.
第六條：
Six:
公平會得到體現
Justice can be dictated.
第七條
Seven:
每個幫派內的兄弟都可以挑戰老大的地位
Any clansmen may challenge for leadership of the clan.
有沒有人想向我挑戰？
Does anyone wish to challenge me?
起立
On your feet.
第八條：
Law Eight:
只有一項懲罰，死！
There's only one penalty. Death.
求你了，求求你了
Please! l'm begging you!
在這裡，有付出就會有回報
You will get out of this army what you put into it.
你工作你就會有得吃
Work and you'll be fed.
你戰鬥你就會被人所尊敬
Fight and you'll be respected.
你戰死你就會被人所懷念
Die and you'll be remembered.
你想著要挑戰我的老大地位？
You thinking of challenging for leadership?
我沒有，長官
No, sir.
我只是個跟隨者...
l'm a follower...
...而不是領導者
...not a leader.
你倒是挺伶牙俐齒的...
You got a smart mouth...
...莎士比亞
...Shakespeare.
你知不知道Getty上校一直追隨著將軍？
You see Colonel Getty always following the General?
但他最後卻向將軍挑戰
He was the last man ever to challenge.
戰鬥持續了6秒...
Fight lasted 6 seconds...
...但將軍沒有殺他
...but he didn't kill him.
只是割下他的舌頭...
Cut off his tongue...
...再割下他的軟蛋
...then he cut off his balls.
而老Getty從此就像只忠誠的狗一樣追隨著將軍
And old Getty's been following him around like a dog ever since.
解散
Fall out!
將軍沒注意...
The General don't see it...
...但是我說你有反骨
...but l say you've got some nigger in you.
這些都是你的？
They're yours?
真是個獨行俠阿？
A solitary man, aren't you?
用望遠鏡可以從遠處觀察生活，而Shakespeare...
Binoculars to watch life from a distance and Shakespeare...
...卻是讀生活而不過日子
...to read about it, instead of living it.
我無意冒犯你 但是你自己好像已經讀過莎士比亞的...
No offense, but you seem to have read Shakespeare...
...作品
...yourself.
如果他想要上檔次 而不是僅僅幹些暗殺之類的...
lf he wishes to rise above mere thuggery...
...一個軍事指揮官必須受過正規傳統的教育...
...a military commander must be classically educated...
...哲學、歷史甚至戲劇敏感性
...philosophy and history, even a sense of the dramatic.
你以為我在戰前是幹什麼工作的？
What do you think that l did before the war?
你以為我是個軍人？
Do you think that l was in the army?
我賣複印機的
l sold copying machines.
我是個銷售員...
l was a salesman...
...卻有著領導天賦 設計並秘密的執行...
...with the talent to lead men, devise and execute a battle plan...
...軍事計劃
...locked away inside.
要不是Nathan Holn的話 我現在還在賣複印機
lf Nathan Holn hadn't come along, l'd still be selling copying machines.
你能想像...
Can you imagine...
...被浪費的生命 你能想像浪費有多嚴重嗎？
...the wasted life? Can you imagine the magnitude of that?
但是戰爭...
But war...
...給了像我這樣的人一個機會
...war gives men like me a chance.
Here.
「獎盃總是名花無主的
''The prize is often left unclaimed.
我們必須鼓起勇氣來...
We must have the courage to grasp it...
...因為未來總是偏愛膽大的人」
...for fortune always favors the bold.''
他總是激勵著我
He always inspires me.
我對未來已經有了設計，一個總體規劃
l have a design for the future. A master plan.
我需要個能幹的軍官來幫我實現
l will need able officers to help me carry it out.
你有這個才能
You have the intelligence.
如果你忠心...
lf your heart matches...
...你可以走得很遠
...you will go far.
我們接下來幾周再詳談
We'll talk more in weeks to come.
解散
Dismissed.
隊長
Captain!
我們明天出發
We'll be moving out tomorrow.
利用望遠鏡作偵查
lssue those binoculars to a scout.
書呢，長官？
And the book, sir?
燒了它
Burn it.
出去
Quit moving!
怎麼樣？
What happened?
-怎麼樣，他怎麼說？ -沒什麼
-What happened? What'd he say? -Nothing.
他有沒有提到我?
Did he say anything about me?
沒有
No!
-我要離開這裡 -你在胡說什麼？
-l'm getting out of here. -What are you talking about?
-逃跑！ -什麼？！
-Escaping. -What?!
你有沒有聽過Saint Rose？ 在海岸邊
You ever hear of Saint Rose? lt's on the coast.
-那是天堂 -我們做不到
-lt's a paradise. -We can't.
我們可以！
We could!
我們三人就能做到
Between the 3 of us we could.
我不行
l can't.
我喜歡這 我喜歡成為一份子的感覺
l like it here. l like being a part of something.
前去看看
Take a point!
有人射了一隻獅子
Some of the men shot a lion.
他們爬進來灌木叢
They crawled into the thicket.
你們這些狗崽子賺了一頓阿
One of you dogs earned a treat.
就在那邊
Over there.
那些人今天早上獵殺了一隻獅子
Those men hunted a lion this morning.
在戰前這裡肯定是個該死的動物園
Must've been a goddamn zoo here before the war.
不管怎樣第三個人得跟著過去
Anyway, a third man went in after it.
我們不知道他是死還是活
We don't know if he's alive or dead.
我需要個志願者
l want a volunteer.
你們中的一個要跟過去
One of you is going in there after him.
我去
l'll go.
我猜個子大的不一定膽大阿
l guess size ain't a measure of courage.
不是嗎？
ls it?
我不這麼想，隊長
l don't think so, Captain!
活著回來，你就可以吃烤獅子了
Come out alive, you get a lion steak!
也許在那你能找到你的Saint Rose
Maybe you'll find your Saint Rose over there.
你還在磨蹭什麼呢，等著聖誕節嗎？
What the hell are you waiting for, Christmas?
為什麼停下來
Why are you stopping?
我找到他了
l found him.
他找到他了
He got him.
我們走
Let's go.
快走
Hurry up!
你還有隻獅子要背呢
You still got a lion to bag!
你們都給我退後
You men get back in line!
-他在那 -快開槍射擊
-There he is! -Shoot him!
跳進水裡 如果找不到他
ln the water. Come back without him...
...你和另外一個人就會替他去死
...and you and another man will die in his place.
快走快走
Go! Go!
我會抓住他的
l'll get him!
走
Go!
不要
Don't.
讓我走吧
Just let me go.
我不想加入你們的軍隊
l don't want to be a part of your army.
我的軍隊？
My army?
我喜歡你這麼說
l like the sound of that.
我逮著他了
l got him!
對不起
l'm sorry.
你怎麼...
How come...
...會這樣...
...you wrecked it...
...對我呢？
...for me?
不是你死就是我活
lt's me or you.
什麼？
What?
可以不這樣的
lt doesn't have to be.
我們可以一起走
We can go together. You and me.
好小子！
Good boy!
Good boy.
抓住他
Get him.
夠了
Finish it!
抓住他
Get him.
這就對了
That's it.
該死的，抓住他
Get him, damn it!
「戰士戰死沙場」
''No harness on my back.''
你在流血?
Bleeding?
嗯，容易流血的傢伙...
Well, bleeder...
...你想著你的Saint Rose?
...you want your Saint Rose?
我會給你你的Saint Rose
l'll give you your Saint Rose.
你好嗎？
How you doing?
這可沒你的份
You shouldn't have.
有條好消息
Here's a piece of good news.
Jerry決定上學了...
Jerry's decided to go to school...
...去獲得他的承包人證書
...to get his contractor's license.
好樣的，Jerry
Good, Jerry.
而小Jimmy想告訴他爺爺他已經...
And little Jimmy wants his grandpa to know that he lost...
...掉了牙了
...a tooth.
謝謝你為了我而呆在那裡
Thanks for being there for me.
「全體男人
''Turn-on's:
穿著制服」
Men in uniform.''
嗨，你們好...
Greetings...
...Pineview, Oregon.
你沿原路返回吧
You just head back the way you came.
Pineview不買任何東西 我們也不想聽你囉嗦...
Pineview ain't buying and we ain't listening...
...而我們也不搞慈善活動
...and we don't give charity.
是嗎？
Really?
夥計我有公務在身
Civilian, l'm on official business.
我得進去這座Pineview的小鎮
l demand entry into the town of Pineview.
你他媽的都在胡說些什麼？
What the hell are you talking about?
夥計，我在和你講話阿
l'm through talking to you, buddy-boy.
去叫你們當家的來把門打開
Get someone with the authority to open this gate.
就是他
That's him.
我是Sheriff Briscoe 你是誰啊？
l'm Sheriff Briscoe. Who the hell are you?
我是美國政府的代表
l'm a representative of the United States government.
我由...
Authorized by...
...重建恢復國會417號令授權...
...Order 4 1 7 of the Restored Congress to reestablish...
...在ldaho以及...
...communication route...
...Oregon...
...in ldaho and...
...傳遞信件
...lower Oregon.
用英語說是什麼意思？
What's that mean in English?
我是你的郵差
l'm your postman.
把槍遞給我
Hand me your gun.
對不起 你得明白...
Beg your pardon. Understand that...
...阻止妨礙郵件違反了聯邦法律...
...tampering with or obstructing the mail is a federal offense...
...Bolin法案要求你們給...
...and the Bolin Act requires that you provide...
...所有的郵差提供...
...all mail carriers with...
...休息地以及...
...sanctuary and...
...營養食品
...nutri-- Food.
給你三秒鐘離開這裡
You got 3 seconds to get out of here.
你知道承包人Jerry嗎？
You know Jerry the contractor?
等一下
Wait a minute.
我從包裡拿些東西出來
l'll get something out of my bag.
你數到一了嗎？
Did you say one?
一
One.
「Paul Davis...
''Paul Davis...
...Pineview14號」
... 1 4 Pineview.''
從沒聽說過這個人 二
Never heard of him. Two.
「Lily May Reno, 林肯路16號」
''Lily May Reno, 1 6 Lincoln Road.''
三
Three.
「lrene March, 沿河路478號」
''lrene March, 4 78 River Road.''
他念的是我名字嗎？
Did he say my name?
我是lrene March.
l'm lrene March.
有封信給你
l have a letter for you.
你讀一下好嗎？
Would you read it?
我肯定它是私人信件
l'm sure it's personal.
-讀吧，總要有個人讀 -我來吧，媽媽
-Please, someone has to. -l'll read it, Mom.
我們在投遞舊的儲存信件...
We're delivering old stockpiles...
...但我收到的都是全新的
...but l'll accept all new correspondence.
「親愛的lrene: 很抱歉我沒有寫信
''Dear lrene: Sorry l haven't written.
每件事都變得很瘋狂
Everything's so crazy.
奇怪的天氣 食物短缺...
The strange weather, the food shortages...
...Nathan Holn農場主帶來了所有這些麻煩
...that farmer Nathan Holn causing all that trouble.
這很難理解
lt's hard to understand.
David的家離軍隊很遠
David's home from the army.
在他到那之前戰爭已經結束了，謝天謝地
The war was over before he even got there. Thank God for that.
我們會為聖誕節想你的...
We're going to miss you for Christmas...
...但是也許得等到來年
...but maybe next year.
奉上我所有的愛」
All our love, Donna.''
我姐姐...
My sister...
...住在Denver...
...in Denver...
...15年前的事了
... 1 5 years ago.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你真是天賜之物
You're a godsend.
救世主
A savior.
我只是...
l'm just...
...郵差
...the postman.
我在路上走了好一段時間了
l've been on the road awhile.
我可不可以找點吃的？
l could use a little something to eat.
可以，當然可以
Yes, absolutely.
還有其它的要求嗎？
ls there anything else?
是的，還有
Yes, there is.
如果鎮上有狗...
lf there are dogs in this town...
...當我在這裡的時候你們得看好它們
...you'll have to leash them while l'm here.
郵差先生
Mr. Postman
嘿，郵差先生 看看，瞧瞧
Hey, Mr. Postman Look and see
如果有一封 一封給我的信
If there's a letter A letter for me
洗乾淨熨好了，先生
Cleaned and pressed, sir.
我掛在那邊
l'll just set them over here.
一位女士把你的褲子改小了
One of the ladies took your pants in.
她認為你瘦了
She thought maybe you lost some weight.
謝謝
Thanks.
有人說過晚餐的事情嗎？
Didn't somebody say something about dinner?
我會帶你帶你到Foster那裡的
l'm supposed to take you to Foster's.
我叫Ford
My name's Ford.
Ford Lincoln Mercury.
我以前叫John Stevens 但我改名字了...
My name used to be John Stevens, but l changed it...
...因為我想開車
...on account of l want to drive cars.
這裡是大家聚會在一起的地方
This is where everybody meet and gather.
你能不能給我們講講關於政府的情況？
Can you tell us about the government?
-告訴我們每一件事 -有沒有總統？
-Tell us everything. -ls there a President?
有的
Yeah.
叫什麼名字?
What's his name?
-你看，我已經非常俄勒 -來吧
-You know, l'm pretty hungry. -Come on.
請！
Please!
他的名字...
His name...
...叫...
...is...
...Richard Starkey
...Richard Starkey.
來自Maine.
From Maine.
他有句名言
He has a saying.
「形勢會越來越好
''Stuff's getting better.
形勢每天都在好轉」
Stuff's getting better every day.''
他是共和黨還是民主黨？
ls he a Democrat or a Republican?
政黨都已經消失了
Parties are over with.
他是獨立當選的
lt's an individual that counts.
那歐洲怎麼樣了？
What about Europe?
歐洲？
Europe?
有沒有消息？
Any word?
嗯，在冰島...
Well, there's...
...空氣非常不錯
...good air in lceland.
Nathan Holn還活著嗎？
ls Nathan Holn still alive?
他死了
He died.
皮膚癌
Skin cancer.
他可能死了...
He may be dead...
...但是Holnists怎麼樣了呢？ 政府都採取什麼行動了？
...but what about the Holnists? What'll the government do about them?
政府還只是剛剛開始做準備
The government's just getting started.
所以你們要靠你們自己堅持6個、8個或者18個月
So you're going to be on your own for 6, 8 or 1 8 months.
海軍陸戰隊怎麼樣了？
How about the Marine Corps?
安靜
Be quiet.
大家安靜
Everyone be quiet.
我們就不能讓他好好吃嗎？
Can't we just let this man eat?
讓我們禱告吧
Let us pray.
感謝你給我們食物
We give you thanks for this food...
今天
...this day...
這個人還有他的好消息
...this man and his good news...
是你答應我們的
...evidence of your promise...
你將會把我們的國家團結在一起
...that you will hold our country together.
阿門
Amen.
跳個舞吧？
Would you like to dance?
我不知道我會不會跳
l don't know if l can.
我想我還只是初學
l think l'm still on duty.
你所要做的就是堅持住
All you have to do is hold on.
有很長時間了
lt's been a long time.
有什麼不對勁嗎？
Something wrong?
你多高？
How tall are you?
六尺高
About six feet.
你聰明嗎？
Are you smart?
比有些人聰明吧，怎麼了？
Smarter than some, l guess. Why?
只是隨便問問
Just wondering.
你有沒有得過腮腺炎？
Have you ever had the bad mumps?
從來沒有
Never had the bad mumps.
也沒有得過梅毒之類的病？
No syphilis, nothing like that?
據你所知...
So as far as you know...
...你精子質量不錯？
...you have good semen?
你在開玩笑？
ls that a trick question?
不，我沒有
No, it's not.
我只是問你...
l'm only asking...
...因為我想讓你使我懷孕
...because l want you to make me pregnant.
好吧...
All right...
...這就對了
...that's it.
等等
Wait.
請等一等
Wait, please.
好像是個穿制服的
lt's got to be the uniform.
這是我丈夫，Michael 他沒有反對
This is my husband, Michael. He hasn't said no.
我什麼也沒說
l haven't said anything yet.
我們連續三年一直都打算要個孩子
We've been trying to have a baby for 3 years.
我們不能指望他 他一歲時就已經的了腮腺炎
We cannot on account of Michael. He had the bad mumps when he was 1 .
所以我們需要一個捐精者
So we need a body father.
我們本可以在這裡找一個 但這樣會帶來很多問題
We could ask a man here, but it may cause problems.
我們見到過這樣的事
We've seen it happen.
在女人沒表現出來以前都沒問題 但之後就很麻煩了
Things go okay until the woman shows, then it can be difficult.
但是你只是路過這裡發發信件
But you'll only be around once in a while with the mail.
你是個郵差
You're the postman.
你覺得怎麼樣？
What do you say, mister?
你得幫我們一個忙
You'd do us a favor.
我會考慮考慮
l'm going to think about it.
請原諒
Excuse me.
我媽媽想給你些東西
My mother would like to give you something.
媽媽，他就在這裡
He's right here, Mom.
這是給我另外一個女兒的...
lt's to my other daughter...
...她叫安妮
...Annie.
信上沒說她在哪
lt doesn't say where.
她五年前離開了這 我們不知道她在哪裡
We don't know where she is. She left 5 years ago.
我們聽說她住在北部
The last we heard she was living up north.
我說，March夫人 你應該知道--
Look, Mrs. March, you should know that--
知道什麼？
lKnow what?
我對你有種直覺
l have a feeling about you.
我知道你會答應我的
l know you'll do what's right.
我得趕緊離開這鬼地方
l got to get out of here.
放鬆，寶貝
Easy, boy.
就在那個角落
lt's right around the corner.
什麼東西？
What is?
你正在找的東西
What you're looking for.
我在找什麼？
What l'm looking for?
瘋狂的老白癡
Crazy old coot.
我就知道你會來的
l knew you'd come here.
是嗎？
You did?
你是如何成為一個郵差的？
So how do you get to be a postman, anyhow?
在正確的時候你得出現在正確的地點
You have to be in the right place at the right time.
我怎麼才能做到呢？
How can l do it?
-我還以為你想要開車呢 -不再想了，那時小孩子的玩意
-l thought you wanted to drive cars. -Not anymore. That's kid's stuff.
這是現實
This is real.
那正確的地點又在哪裡？
So where's the right place?
你知道，可能在任何時間的任何地點
Could be anywhere, you know. Anytime.
只有另外一個郵差才能讓你成為一個郵差
Only another postman can make you a postman.
就像吸血鬼那樣？
lKind of like vampires, right?
對，有點像那樣
Yeah, something like that.
你必須得發誓
You have to be sworn in, so....
郵局有些不太穩定，也許持續不了多久
The organization's kind of shaky right now. lt might not last.
怎麼發誓？
What does?
你將會碰到一些根本不信任你的人
You'd meet people who don't believe in you.
我會和他們坦誠相待
l'll set them straight.
郵差是個孤獨的工作
lt's a lonely job.
我這一生都孤獨
l've been lonely all my life.
我也一樣，Ford
So have l, Ford.
我也一樣啊
So have l.
真該死！
What the hell!
你跟著我念
You repeat after me.
「無論大雪還是...
''Neither snow...
還是暴雨...
...nor rain...
無論是炎炎烈日...
...nor heat...
還是漆黑夜晚...
...nor gloom of night...
郵差...
...stays these couriers...
都會迅速的完成他們的任務」
...from the swift completion of their appointed rounds.''
好了，可以了
Okay, then.
不，我說可以了 你聽就行了
No, l'm saying that. You just listen.
對不起
l'm sorry.
經過我的授權，現在你可以投遞這些信件了
By my authority you're now empowered to carry the mail.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你是個郵差了
You're a postman.
為了送信我會萬死不辭
l'd die to get a letter through.
你說什麼？
What did you say?
-我說，為了送信我會萬死不辭 -Johnny!
-l said l'd die to get a letter through. -Johnny!
你怎麼還不走開
Why don't you run along.
我要和他說幾句話
l need to speak to this man.
我待會再找你
l'll see you around.
就這麼說定了，Ford
Sure thing, Ford.
Johnny對你印象很好 整個鎮子的人對你印象都很好
Johnny is impressed with you. Whole town is impressed with you.
我猜不包括你吧
l take it you're not.
-你比你看起來的要聰明的多 -有什麼可以效勞的？
-You're smarter than you look. -What can l do for you?
要麼你自己自動消失要麼我把你趕走 兩條路隨你挑
You can either clear out or l can throw you out. Either way suits me.
你還沒搞明白 我是由政府授權的--
You don't understand. l'm a government employee authorized by--
你被授權個屁！
You are not authorized by shit!
你只是逃難到了這裡 你只不過是個...
You were trying to sneak out of here. You are nothing...
發現了一袋信件的流浪漢 我要你滾出我的鎮子
...but a drifter who found a bag of mail. l want you out of town.
好吧，我會把這都寫進我的報告
All right. This is going in my report.
郵差先生，這裡的人們不需要夢想
These people don't need dreams, Mr. Postman.
他們需要一些實際的東西 他們需要Holnists的幫助
They need something real. They need help with the Holnists.
你能帶給他們這些嗎？
Are you going to bring them that?
我想不能吧
Didn't think so.
到目前為止你帶給我們的只是 幾碗湯還有幾顆破碎的心
All you cost us so far is a few bowls of soup and maybe a few broken hearts.
我要這個地方保持原樣
l aim to keep it that way.
你可以在這待到明天早上...
You can stay here till morning...
以後我就再也不想看見你了
...then l don't ever want to see you again.
Benning
''Benning.
Portland
Portland.
Boston？
Boston''?
這些傢伙--
What the hell these people--
走開
Just leave it.
我叫你走開
l said, leave it.
Saint Rose？
''Saint Rose''?
你好，Abby
Hello, Abby.
你明天就要走了？
You'll be leaving tomorrow?
是吧
l guess.
每個人都在熬夜寫信 等著你幫他們帶走
Everybody's up late writing letters for you to take.
他們都很興奮
They're so excited.
那你呢？你寫信了沒有？
And how about you? Do you have a letter?
我不知道要寫給誰
l don't have anybody to write to.
我可以給你找個筆友
l'll find you a pen pal.
就是有著相同愛好的一些人
Someone with similar interests. You know?
比如說跳舞了，還有...
Like dancing and...
檢查腮腺炎
...checking for mumps.
你很風趣
You're funny.
鎮上的人幾乎都不懂風趣了
Hardly anybody's funny around here.
你已經決定了沒有？
Have you decided yet?
我一直都在考慮
Been thinking about it.
當然了
Sure.
我是說...
l mean...
為什麼不呢？
...why not?
天啊，你真是太....
God, you're so....
你太...
You're so...
漂亮了
...beautiful.
對不起，也許你希望這更像是個醫療手術
l'm sorry, you probably want to keep things more clinical.
你甚至不知道我的名字
You don't even know my name.
我不想知道
l don't want to.
如果你把眼睛閉上的話...
lt would be easier for me...
我會覺得更自然
...if you closed your eyes.
郵差先生，我們經過討論
We took a vote, Mr. Postman.
希望你能收下
We want you to have this.
所以你不能拒絕
So you can't say no.
我收下了
l'll take it.
一捲鋪蓋、一些麥片還有一周的乾糧
You got a bedroll, some oats and a week's rations.
很好
Good.
謝謝
Thank you.
你要往哪裡走？
Where will you go from here?
哪裡？
Go?
西方...
West...
然後我又會再返回來
...then l'll work my way...
就像走個"8"字形
...back here, sort of a figure eight.
現在的情況是困難了點
Times seem hard right now.
但是你們要堅信會越來越好的
But you got to believe things are getting better.
鳥兒又開始遷徙了
Birds are migrating again.
雨季來臨了
The rains are back.
局勢...
Stuff's....
局勢正在逐漸好轉
Stuff's getting better.
Oh beautiful
For spacious skies
For amber waves of grain
該死
Shit!
無論你是誰 你還是顯得有些緊張
You've got a hell of a nerve, whoever you are.
今天早上你看見Abby了嗎？
Did you see Abby around this morning?
我就送你到這裡了
This is as far as l go.
你自己上路吧
You're on your own.
God shed his grace on thee
And crown thy good
With brotherhood
你真的像你說的是個郵差嗎？
Are you really who you say you are?
如果我帶著信件回來...
lf l come back with some mail...
你就會相信了
...you'll know.
該死
Goddamn it!
你看什麼？
What are you looking at?
全身
Everything.
他們通常不看我的
They don't usually look at me.
那個...
Who is responsible...
...是誰幹的？
...for that?
我說...
l said...
...那是
...''Who's responsible...
誰幹的？
...for that''?!
Holnists,Johnny 你得呆在--
Holnists, Johnny. You got to stay--
-你不能讓他們發現 -我是個郵差！
-You got to stay out of sight. -l'm a postman!
我不會當逃兵的！
And l'm not running from anybody!
呆在這裡 不然我會親自把你鎖起來！
Stay out of this, or l will lock you up myself.
你得負責
You'll be responsible.
去把旗子燒了
Now set that flag on fire.
從窗戶扔進郵局
Throw it through the window of your post office.
快照辦，Michael
Do it, Michael.
沒事的，Michael，快照辦
lt's all right, Michael. Throw it.
美利堅合眾國...
The United States...
...並不存在！
...doesn't exist!
那面國旗就是垃圾
That flag is an abomination!
有一個最奇怪的小山羊 它躲在柵欄後面....
There was the strangest little goat and it was behind a fence and it....
我看著它而它臉色就變了
l looked at it and it had a color to it.
不錯
Good.
都不錯
Everything.
我很吃驚 難道它是....
l was amazed. lt was....
真不賴！
Good Lord!
先生們，那個...
That, gentlemen...
是第一流的美臀
...is a first-rate piece of ass.
去叫鎮長給我引見一下 她這種美人不屬於這種小地方的
Tell the sheriff to introduce me. She doesn't belong in this mudhole.
請原諒
Excuse me.
又是你啊
You again!
她是我老婆，將軍
That's my wife, General.
她已經結婚了
She's a married woman.
是嗎？
Really?
你知道我們在這裡執行的是什麼政府體制嗎？
Do you know what system of government we have here?
我們執行的是所謂的聯邦體系 就像中世紀那樣
We have what is known as a feudal system, like in the Middle Ages.
君主和臣子 就像你和我
That's lords and vassals. That's you and me.
現在那些君主
Now those lords...
他們有些想法
...they had some ideas.
他們認為如果一個臣子結婚了
They believed that if a vassal got married...
那君主就有權...
...it was the lord's right...
有權...
...his right...
享有和臣子的新娘過夜的「初夜權」
...to sleep with the bride on the wedding night.
我和Abby已經結婚三年了
Me and Abby have been married 3 years.
真遺憾我沒有被邀請參加你們的婚禮
l'm sorry, but l wasn't invited to the wedding.
你已經幫我一個忙了
You've already done me one favor, son.
不要讓這件事成為你的一個污點
Don't let this be a black mark on an otherwise perfect record.
我們都是斯文人
We'll be civilized about this.
我希望你能祝福我
l want you to give me your blessing.
先生，我做不到
Sir, l can't.
你做不到？
You can't?
你做不到
You can't.
做不到
''Can't.''
我們曾有個偉大的國家
We had a great nation once.
我知道它為什麼能偉大
lKnow what made it great?
因為「我做得到」
''l can.''
直到弱智們來了
Till the weak came along.
「我做不到」破壞了我們
The ''l can'ts'' destroyed us!
我現在就要讓我們重新強大起來
l'm going to make us strong again.
我要成為一個新國家的...
l'm going to be the father...
...國父
...of a new nation.
你知不知道為什麼...
And do you know why...
...會是我呢？
...it will be me?
因為「我做得到」
Because l can.
快住手
Stop it!
你殺死他了
You're killing him!
讓我過去
Let me go!
求你了讓我過去吧
Please, let me go!
幫幫他啊，誰能幫幫他啊
Help him, somebody! Please!
你大可不必--
You didn't have to--!
不必什麼？
Didn't have to what?
你個混蛋！
You bastard!
是你殺了他
You killed him!
你的人好像很不安分阿
Your people seem seditious.
你好像也不安分
You seem seditious.
我看見的都是什麼呢？
What am l seeing here?
我在等著呢！
l'm waiting!
有個人帶著信件來過這 他說他是個郵差
A man came through with mail. Said he was a postman.
他說東部的政府已經重建起來了
Said that the government had been restored back east.
什麼政府？
What government?
美國政府！
The United States government!
誰說的？
Who said that?
他往哪個方向走了？
Which way did he go?
不要讓我再問第二遍
Do not make me ask again.
東邊
East.
派一隊人去東邊
Send a patrol east!
再派三隊人...
Send 3 more...
...去北邊，南邊和西邊！
...north, south and west!
他們最好是在東邊找到他
They'd better find him east.
快把那T恤脫了，Johnny!
Take that damn shirt off, Johnny!
我已經保護了這些信件
l managed to save these.
你也想死嗎？
Do you want to die too?
我要帶著這些信件去南方
l'm headed south with the mail.
別發傻了
Don't be a fool.
那我該怎麼辦？
What should l be?
Rachel Clark.
Charlie Sykes
''Charlie Sykes.''
Graham Drewitt
''Graham Drewitt.''
G.D在去年冬天得流感死了
G.D. died of flu last winter.
就這麼多了
That's all there is.
夥計們，就這麼多了
That's all there is, folks.
目前而已
For now.
將來會有更多的 只要有個郵局系統的存在
But there'll be more, lots more, once there's a real system in place.
對吧？
Right?
紐約城怎麼樣了？
What about New York City?
他們有沒有從這場災難中倖存下來？
Did they survive the plague?
倖存？
Survive?
他們修復了百老匯並重新開張了
They got Broadway up and running again.
還有個小孩演Andrew Floyd Webber 你肯定不敢相信
There's a kid doing Andrew Floyd Webber, you wouldn't believe.
發一封信要多少錢？
How much is it to mail a letter?
發一封
''Mail....''
他們不肯開城門
They won't open the gates.
他們說他們有個來自美國政府的代表
They say they got a representative of the Restored United States in there.
他們說我們的軍隊是非法的
They say this army is illegal.
-他們還說-- -快去死吧!
-And they say-- -Drop dead!
下地獄吧！
And go to hell!
他們就這麼說的
That's what they say.
你們在幹嗎？ 快開城門
What are you doing?! Open the gates.
ldiots!
你都在想些什麼？！
What're you thinking?!
《羅馬書》上...
The Romans...
有句話...
...had an expression...
常被用來嚇唬小孩子
...they used to scare their children.
「Hannibal...
''Hannibal...
...ad portas」
...ad portas!''
Hannibal...
...就在門口
...is at the gates.
你知道Hannibal是誰嗎?
Do you know who Hannibal was?
當然不知道
Of course not.
像你這麼漂亮的女孩當然不會明白這種事情了
A pretty girl like you wouldn't understand something like that.
-讓我們和他們打吧！ -用什麼打？
-Let's fight them! -With what?
我們有五把槍 卻一發子彈也沒有
We've got 5 guns, maybe 0 rounds of ammo.
就這些武器我們怎麼和他們打？
How we going to fight with that?
你們不要打
You don't.
和他們談判吧
Negotiate a settlement.
給他們些額外的補給
Give them extra supplies.
告訴他們，你是政府的代表
You're the government rep. Tell them.
就在這裡
Right here.
快點 我還有個攻擊計劃要制定
Make it quick. l've got an attack to coordinate.
他們叫我來訂個和平條約
They've asked me to negotiate a peace treaty.
我認識你嗎？
Do l know you?
我不這樣認為，先生
l don't think so, sir.
你就是郵差
You're the postman.
是嗎?
Aren't you?
進去!
lnside!
美國的信
''U.S. Mail.''
重建後的美國
''The Restored United States of America.''
這裡的人真的相信這些狗屎?!
Do these people really believe that shit?!
說真的，你到底是誰?
Who are you, really?
我是一個美國的郵差...
l'm a United States postman...
...通過重建的國會第417號命令授權
...authorized by Order 4 1 7 of the Restored Congress.
我參加了Georgetown戰役 我親眼目睹白宮被夷為平地
l was at the Battle of Georgetown. l watched the White House burn down.
你別想讓我...
Do not try to sell me...
...相信那所謂的重建的美國!
...on any Restored United States!
新的首都建在Minneapolis...
The new capital is based in Minneapolis...
...在Hubert Humphrey的地下宮殿裡面
...inside the Hubert Humphrey Metrodome.
你知道過去的維京人在什麼地方玩耍嗎?
You know where the Vikings used to play?
你在開玩笑吧
You're funny.
條件是什麼?
What are the terms?
他們將打開大門, 給與平常雙倍的物資...
They'll open the gates, give double the usual...
...只是...
...just...
...不要傷害任何人
...don't hurt anybody.
這一切只是一個誤會
This was all a misunderstanding.
我讚賞你的提議,郵差先生
l appreciate your offer, Mr. Postman.
但事實是你根本沒有資格來討價還價
But the fact is that you're in no position to negotiate.
這裡的人造成了瘋狂和暴亂...
These people made it through the bugs and the riots...
...還有長達三年的冬天, 但是他們並不想讓你倖存
...and the 3-year winters, but they're not going to survive you.
給我開火!
Fire at will!
法律第六條:
Law Six:
法律就是...
Justice can be...
...命令!
...dictated!
殺了他, 把重建的美國和他一起殺了
lKill him, and kill the Restored United States with him.
根據法律第8條...
ln accordance with Law 8...
...以及緊急事件授權第46號命令...
...and by the authority of Emergency Order 46...
...你將因此--
...you are hereby--
抓住她!
Get her!
快去, 抓住他!
Go on, get him!
我們現在不能停
We can't stop now.
你怎麼了?
What are you...?
噢，上帝呀!
Oh, God!
趴下
Come on down.
別動
Don't move.
如果你有子彈,你早開槍了
lf you had a bullet, you'd use it.
快走
Come on.
我想我很久沒喝過湯了
l don't think l ever had water soup before.
也許下次我們應該試著放點鹽
Maybe next time we could try it with a little sand.
泥土
Dirt.
也許只是一點佐料
Maybe a twig garnish.
你總是認為我很好笑
You used to think l was funny.
他們殺了Michael
They killed Michael.
我很難過
l'm sorry.
你難過什麼?
How sorry are you?
什麼?
What?
你這樣問什麼意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
你怎麼了?
What's with you?
你身上有個8的印記
You have the mark of 8 on you.
印記並不表示--
Mark doesn't mean--
你是個騙子
You're a liar.
你和Bethlehem在一起
You were with Bethlehem.
你也是他們的一分子?
Does that make you one of them?
別逼我用這個
Don't make me use this.
起風了
Wind's come up.
越來越冷了
It's getting colder too.
另一場暴風就要來了
Must be another storm.
還要什麼?
Anything else?
我不是說要你....
l didn't mean for you to....
你再不下床走動你的腿就要爛掉
Your legs are going to rot off if you don't try to walk.
-我受傷了 -你懶惰!
-l'm hurt. -You're lazy!
懶惰?
Lazy?
我的胃上穿了一個洞...
l got a hole in my stomach...
...而且我很虛弱
...and l'm weak.
這周圍只有雪和草...
The  big meals around here are snow and grass...
...而且我們的草就要用完了
...and we're running out of grass.
你要幹什麼?
What're you doing?
把早餐給我吧!
Give me a break!
我去檢查一下關口
l'm going to check the pass.
你為什麼這麼著急?
Why are you in such a hurry?
我們可以考慮一下更糟的地方
l could think of worse places.
或者更糟的軍隊
Or l could think of worse company.
好極了!
Perfect!
救命!
Help!
Please!
快來呀!
Quick!
上帝呀, 救救我!
God, help me!
我告訴你了我沒事
l told you that's all there was.
正因為如此你該吃了它
That's why you should have it.
我知道你能走
l knew you could walk.
你真奇怪
You're weird.
你知道嗎？?
lKnow that?
我曾經在月亮上走過, Abby
We walked on the moon once, Abby.
真的?
So?
但現在有什麼好?
What good is that now?
顯然你忘記了...
Obviously you've forgotten...
...唐，和...
...Tang and...
...微波爐，還有....
...microwave ovens and....
你的臉看起來很可愛
Your face looks pretty.
我的意思是...
l mean...
...如果沒受傷
...not so bruised.
其實...
Look...
...有些事你應該知道
...there's something you'd better know.
你很快就能發現
You're going to find out soon enough.
我懷孕了
l'm pregnant.
是Michael的孩子
lt's Michael's baby.
但其實你才是真正的父親
You're just the body father.
你怎麼知道是我的...
How do you know it's mine...
...不是Bethlehem的?
...not Bethlehem's?
他每天晚上都和我在一起
He tried with me almost every night.
但是他不行...
He couldn't do it...
...所以他打我
...so he beat me.
還說是我的錯
Said it was my fault.
對不起, Abby
l'm sorry, Abby.
怎麼了?
What is it?
出什麼事了?
What's wrong?
是孩子嗎?
ls it the baby?
那個關口空了
The pass is clear.
發生了什麼事?
What happened?
還好，你把我們的東西搬出來了
Good, you got our stuff out.
當然
Of course.
什麼?
What?
我不明白
l don't understand.
火是我放的
l set the fire.
難道你認為我們要永遠呆在這裡嗎?
Did you think we'd stay here forever?
當然不是
No.
如果你能和我一起走 給孩子找一個安全的地方我會很感激的...
l'd appreciate it if you'd walk with me to find someplace safe for the baby...
...否則我們就分開
...then we can split up.
你刮臉了
You shaved.
看起來不錯
Looks nice.
你真是很奇怪!
You're really weird!
你知道嗎?
You know that?
你聽說過Saint Rose嗎, Abby?
You ever heard of Saint Rose, Abby?
我聽別人說過
l've heard people talk.
我聽過很多名字...
l've heard lots of names...
...Bliss, Hesperia, 還有New Eden
...Bliss, Hesperia, and New Eden.
Sheriff Briscoe 說這是幻想
Sheriff Briscoe says it's a fantasy.
他錯了
He's wrong.
Saint Rose 就在那裡...
Saint Rose is out there...
...我要找到它
...and l'm going to find it.
但你是郵差
But you're the postman.
我誰也不是, Abby
l'm nobody, Abby.
我討厭這樣
This is what l hate.
陌生人
Strangers.
你是對她說 嗨, 還是把她攔下來?
Do you say hi, or do you blow their heads off?
他們到底想分享他們所有的還是奪去你有的?
Do they want to share what they got or take what you have?
如果他們想要奪取,你怎麼去阻止他們?
lf they want to take, how far are you willing to go to stop them?
好了, 停在那兒
All right, that's far enough.
我們不想惹麻煩
We don't want any trouble.
我也不想,先生
Me neither, mister.
你是誰?
What are you?
18號郵遞員...
Carrier 1 8...
...美國郵政服務
...U.S. Postal Service.
有信嗎?
Got any mail?
那不可能
That's impossible.
你沒聽說過郵差嗎?
Ain't you heard of The Postman?
沒有
No.
告訴我們
Tell us.
他是倖存的最偉大的人
He's only the greatest man who ever lived.
他穿過荒地...
He crossed the wasteland...
...用拳頭把敵人打倒...
...shook his fist at the enemy...
...把口水吐到Bethlehem將軍的眼睛裡
...and spit in the eye of General Bethlehem himself.
他現在和Starkey總統一起從東邊回來了
He's back east with President Starkey right now.
誰告訴你這些?
Who told you all this?
郵局局長Ford Lincoln Mercury
Postmaster Ford Lincoln Mercury.
他親自參加了重建的國會
He's in direct contact with the restored Congress.
親自參加?!
Direct contact?!
我不相信!
l don't believe this!
郵遞員營地!
Carrier camp!
大家集合!
Gather around, everybody!
快,集合 又來了一封信
Come on, gather around. Got another letter here.
昨晚到的
lt came in last night.
-這兒怎麼了? -郵差送給Ford又一封信
-What's all this? -The Postman sent Ford another letter.
他要讀了
He's going to read it.
你們好，郵遞員們
''Hello, all postal carriers.
我現在在Minneapolis和Starkey總統在一起...
l'm here in Minneapolis with President Starkey...
...但我的心跟你們在一起
...but my thoughts are with you.
請記住...
Remember...
...沒有什麼值得整晚去做
...nothing worth doing can be done overnight.
抬起你的頭盡力別被擊中
lKeep your chins up and do your best not to get shot.
你們是...
Signed...
...郵差 !
...The Postman'' !
他的信總是很短
His letters are always kind of short.
等等! 還有一個附言
Hold on! There's a P.S.
有人知道附言代表什麼?
Does anybody know what P.S. stands for?
-天哪! -那是H.S., Eddie
-Holy shit! -That would be H.S., Eddie.
當我在Pineview生活時我見過他
No, l saw him once when l lived in Pineview.
它就是郵差
lt's The Postman.
我猜你會說這個
Guess you want to talk about this.
我找到他了! 我找到他了!
l found him! l found him!
Minneapolis?
''Minneapolis?''
P.S. Ford知道做什麼?
''P.S. Ford knows what to do?''
這是什麼?
What is this?
這都是什麼? 這究竟是什麼--
What is all this? What the hell--
我撒謊了!
l lied!
我告訴人們你親自和我聯繫了
l told people you were in direct contact with me.
-為什麼? -因為我不想就這樣結束
-Why? -Because l didn't want it to end.
看...
Look...
...我不知道我能呆多久 我是說...
...l don't know how long l can stay. l mean...
...Starkey總統...
...President Starkey...
...他一旦傳話給我我又要走
...he's going to send word for me one day and then l'll have to move on.
你明白嗎?
Do you understand?
但你一直會呆到他傳話來, 對嗎?
But you'll stay until he sends word, right?
別這樣 把手放下
Don't do that. Hands down.
你會一直呆到Starkey總統傳話過來,對嗎?
You're staying till President Starkey sends word, right?
對!
Yes!
直到他傳話，沒錯
Until he sends word. Right.
你能說一些話讓他們知道真的是你?
Could you say a few words just so they know it's really you?
我就是（郵差）
lt's me.
下來了
Coming down.
我們先把所有信件運到這裡
We bring all the mail here first.
分揀
We sort it.
編組 再送出去
We group it. Then it goes out.
到目前為止，我們已經有30條線路了
So far, we got 30 routes.
你把tyranny寫錯了
You spelled ''tyranny'' wrong.
天哪!
Boy!
他太帥了
He's smart.
快速地完成...
From the swift completion...
...指定的任務
...of their appointed rounds.
祝賀大家，你們現在是美國郵遞員了
Congratulations. You are now U.S. postal carriers.
你多大了?
How old are you?
我68了,先生
l'm 68, sir.
我能問你一個問題嗎?
Can l ask you a question?
你能騎馬嗎?
Can you ride?
不能
No.
也不能走太遠
Can't walk too good either.
那你為什麼要來這裡?
So why are you here?
我知道材料學
l know stuff.
你在哪兒刻的?
Where did you get that?
1970年
1 9 70.
一個大眼睛女孩兒...
A girl with eyes as big as saucers...
...在一個叫Saigon的小鎮給我刻的
...did me in a little town called Saigon.
Ford讓我住他的地方
Ford wants me to have his place.
他說是最好的
Said it's the best.
我在另一邊
l'm on the other side.
我在這兒有很多屋子
l got plenty of room here.
和制服一樣多
So much for the uniform theory.
他是在Oregon邊界被抓住的
He was captured on the Oregon border.
你到底是誰?
Who the hell are you?
12號郵遞員
Carrier 1 .
美國郵政服務
United States Postal Service.
我要隊伍在拂曉之前動身
l want the camp struck at dawn.
我們將向北行進!
We'll be moving north!
你把tyranny寫錯了
You spelled ''tyranny'' wrong.
我希望他們停止喝酒
l wish they'd stop saluting.
注意安全
Just stay safe.
記住...
Remember...
...郵遞員比郵件重要
...the mailman's more important than the mail.
天哪，他太帥了
Boy, he's smart.
在我小的時候我經常把帽子朝後
When l was a kid we used to turn our hat around backwards.
我認為比較酷
Thought it was cool.
上帝保佑!
Jesus Christ!
該死!
Damn!
我錯過了
l missed him.
這個鎮叫什麼?
What's the name of this town?
我們從來沒有給它命名
We never named it.
我宣佈...
l officially declare...
...10號郵政所...
...Postal Station Number 1 0...
...在Elvis, Oregon...
...in Elvis, Oregon...
...正式開業
...open for business.
從現在開始你們可以把信件送到下面去，好嗎?
From now on you got to get your mail down there, okay?
這個看來不能用了
This one doesn't work.
再讀一遍
Read it again.
你確定?
Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
親愛的媽媽：聽到你的消息真是奇跡
''Dearest Mom: What a miracle to hear from you.''
生活在變好
Stuff is getting better.
生活每天都在變好
Stuff is getting better every day.
我不認識你...
l don't know who you are...
...但我知道我錯怪你了
...but l do know l was wrong about you.
鎮長，你也有一封信
Got a letter for you too, Sheriff.
這是我妹妹來的信
lt's from my sister.
我還以為她死了
Thought she was dead.
你想錯了
You thought wrong.
想跳支舞嗎?
Would you like to dance?
Well, they say that you can never
Never go back home
And if you're bound to wander
You're bound to be alone
You say I got no right
To feel what I feel
When I look into your eyes
跳個舞好嗎?
Want to dance?
But that I dream of you
Most every night
Comes as no surprise
Well, I've been Out on this road for so long
Far and wide
Do I roam
But something in your smile tells me
I'm almost home
I was lost in the dark
All alone
Till the light
In your eyes showed me
I was almost
Home is where the heart is
And my heart goes with you
I would travel till the end of time
If that's what I have to do
Just to spend one night
Till your sweet love light
Come down
Shining down on me
喂喂
Hello.
你在跟誰說話?
Who do you talk to?
試了7年了什麼都沒有...
Not a soul in 7 years of trying...
...但是我願意
...but l will.
來點嗎?
Want some?
不了，謝謝
No, thanks.
別讓孩子看見這些
Don't let the kids see that.
你帶個頭,看看
You go ahead, take a look.
我是一個航空工程師
l was an aerospace engineer.
我幫助設計了伽利略號宇宙空間站
l helped design the Galileo Space Station.
真的?
No shit?
真的
No shit.
我曾夢想它繞著地球永遠轉下去...
l dream it's orbiting the Earth forever...
...裝著一打死人骨頭...
...with a dozen human skeletons...
...對著別人咧著嘴笑...
...all grinning at each other...
...嘲笑我們下面這些人
...laughing at us down here.
-怎麼了? -是Tony
-What is it? -lt's Tony.
他遲到了
He's overdue.
那是5號
That makes 5.
所有南方的路線
All on southern routes.
還是孩子
Just children.
你給我的都是孩子
You bring me children.
我要一個男人
l want a man.
我們知道出生和...
We got births and...
...死亡
...deaths.
知道天氣 大部分談話
Got weather. Mostly gossip.
這裡什麼都沒有
There's nothing here.
什麼都沒有?
Nothing?
所有的...
Everything...
...都在這
...is here.
我是唯一看見這些的?!
Am l the only one who sees that?!
什麼?
What?
一個軍人,特別是個指揮官...
A military man, especially a commander...
...應該有一本帳
...should keep a journal.
在他死後,這是唯一的防禦...
After he's gone, it's the only real defense...
...對付那些後來出現的誹謗
...against the slander that later arises.
告訴我你還知道些什麼
Tell me about the other stuff you know.
糟糕!
Shit!
把屍體抬走
Get rid of the bodies.
我不想讓這些人怪我們所做的
l don't want these people blamed for what we did.
無論大雪還是暴雨 無論是炎炎烈日還是漆黑夜晚...
Neither snow, nor rain, nor gloom of night...
...穿過強盜的地獄, 穿過戰火...
...through bandit's hell, through firefight...
...穿過洪水和瘟疫 我們不能失敗...
...through flood and plague we cannot fail...
...什麼都不能阻止郵件
...no Holnist trash will stop the mail.
你現在是美國郵遞員
You are now U.S. Postal Carriers.
他們修改了誓詞
They changed the oath.
Ford的主意
Ford's idea.
身份
Figures.
他們從來沒問過他們要取代誰...
They don't think to ask who they're replacing...
...或者為什麼
...or why.
先生?
Sir?
如果能和您握手我會感到很光榮的
lt'd be an honor if l could shake your hand.
我認識你嗎?
Do l know you?
我想不認識
l don't think so.
好運
Good luck, then.
好孩子
Nice kid.
要不了多久你就沒命了
He'll probably be dead in a week.
現在不是你的錯
Now that is not your fault.
你已經精疲力盡了，你需要休息 那裡有食物--
You're exhausted. You need rest. There's food--
-你去哪兒? -22號路線
-Where are you going? -Route .
你下來 下馬
You're grounded. Get off the horse.
你知道規則的
You know the rule.
什麼規則?
What rule?
22號太靠近南邊了 下馬
, it's too far south. Get off the horse.
但是他們在等著--
But they're waiting on--
你快給我下馬！
Get off the goddamn horse!
我回來處理的
l'll tie him off to this one.
你不能再這麼做了
You can't keep doing this!
-做什麼？ -跑所有的線路
-Doing what? -Riding all the routes.
你這樣救不了任何人
You're not saving anybody.
我有沒有告訴你我怎樣成為一個郵差的？
Did l ever tell you how l got to be a postman?
我不知道你是哭還是笑
l don't know if you'd laugh or cry.
那是什麼？
What is it?
當心！
Watch out!
著火了，快跑
We got fire! Move!
-郵資欠費 -Elvis巡邏
-''Postage due.'' -Elvis patrol.
你想要挑起戰爭嗎？
You want a war?
你想要挑起戰爭嗎？！
You want a war?!
我就跟你來場...
l'll give you...
硬仗！
...a war!
我就是為戰爭
l was...
而生！
...born for it!
兇手！
You murderers!
你以為你可以騎馬？
You think you can ride?!
那今天就是你的幸運日
Then today's your lucky day!
Bethlehem說...
Bethlehem says...
他會向北進攻
...he's headed north.
他將在每個鎮子殺死10個人...
He's going to kill 1 0 people in every town...
再在地上焚燒他們屍體 以此來報復你
...then burn it to the ground for what you did.
他說他會到Pineview去
He said that Pineview's on his way.
他將會在那裡等你 但不會等太久
He'd wait there for you, but not for long.
我很害怕
l was so scared, sir.
我以為他們會殺了我
l thought they were going to kill me too.
看見沒？
See?
我早告訴過你，我們來得太晚了
We're too late. l told you.
你打算怎麼辦？
What're you going to do?
我要阻止他們
l'm going to stop this.
你不能
You can't.
你給我讓開，都給我讓開
Get out of the way, Ford. All of you!
他們會殺了你的
They'll kill you!
攔住他
Hold him!
住手
Stop it!
-你們傷著他了 -沒有
-You're hurting him! -l'm not!
傷著了
Yes, you are!
沒有，我們沒傷害他
l'm not! l'm not hurting him.
這都是因為我 我沒有執行你的命令
This is all my doing. l went against your orders.
你叫我埋了那些死屍 但我把他們送到Bethlehem那裡了
You told me to bury the dead Holnists, but l sent them Bethlehem.
為什麼？
Why?
我們得讓Bethlehem知道 我們永不放棄
Bethlehem has to know we won't stop!
真是該死
Goddamn it, Ford!
那些人是因我們而死啊
Those people are dying because of us!
他們因為我們所做的才死的阿
They're dying because of what we did.
不是的 他們是因為Bethlehem才死的
They're not! They're dying because of Bethlehem...
因為這是個狗屎世界 如果我們要想改變它
...because this is a shitty world! lf we're going to change it...
就總會有人要犧牲
...then someone might have to die.
如果我可以替他們在下面受死 我願意，但我做不到
lf l could make it be me down there, l would, but l can't!
不要啊，求你們了
No! Please!
-你，滾開 -攔住她
-You, out here! -Hold her!
求求你了
Please!
他就在某個地方
He's out there somewhere.
看著我們
Watching.
我能感覺得到
l can feel it.
你也感覺到了，不是嗎？
You feel it too, don't you?
鎮長，本來大可不必如此
lt didn't have to end like this, Sheriff!
他知道我在哪裡 如果他是個男人他就會現身
He knew where l'd be if he wanted to face me like a man!
但他卻像個兔子一樣
lnstead he's hiding...
躲起來了
...like a rabbit!
你們的郵差也不過如此
So much for your Postman!
中尉！
Lieutenant!
有!
Ready!
我們甚至不知道他們的名字
We don't even know their names.
我知道
We know their names.
那個就是我父親
l think that's my dad.
瞄準！
Aim!
繼續前進阿，郵差！
Ride, Postman!
繼續前進！
Ride!
你聽見了嗎？!
You hear me?!
我叫你們繼續前進！
l said, ''Ride!''
射擊！
Fire!
天哪，我都幹了些什麼啊！
My God, what have l done?
Ford所做的是錯的
What Ford did was wrong!
但我們卻沒有採取任何的措施
But it doesn't change anything...
來進行補救，不是嗎？
...for any of us, does it?
人都在這了？
ls this everybody?
其餘的還在趕路
The rest are on the overdue list.
那就是都在這了
Then this is everybody.
有封來自總統的信
Got a letter from the President.
你們好，郵遞員們！
''Greetings, all carriers.''
總統好！
Greetings, President Starkey!
我一直都在和郵差保持聯絡
''l've been in contact with The Postman.
我收到了所有的報告
And l've received all the reports.
我為你們自豪
l'm proud of you all.
在暗無天日的日子裡 在這個黑暗的世界裡
ln dark days, in a weary world...
你們付出了所有，卻一無所求
...you gave everything and asked for nothing.
你們打退絕望，重拾希望
You beat back despair and replaced it with hope.
而你的國家卻無法給你們任何回報
For that, your country can never repay you.
但是付出的代價太大
But the price is too high...
而我也不想再看到我的勇士們有任何的犧牲
...and l won't see any more of my bravest die.
職責所在，我將要解散...
lt is my duty to hereby disband...
重建的美國的郵政服務
...the Postal Service of the Restored United States.
請將你們的制服都燒掉...
You are to burn your uniforms...
而郵差也將立即返回Minneapolis
...and The Postman is to return to Minneapolis at once.
謝謝
Thank you.
上帝保佑你們
And God bless you all.
總統敬上
The President.''
總統從沒寫過這樣的信
The President never wrote that letter.
如果他能寫信的話 他就會這麼寫的
lf he could've, that's what he would have said.
還有一封信是給誰的？
Who's the other letter to?
Bethlehem.
-我早上就把信送過去 -信上說什麼？
-l'm taking it to him in the morning. -What's it say?
-內容保密，你知道這是規矩 -信上到底怎麼說的？
-Mail's private, you know that. -What does it say?
信上說要結束了
lt says it's over.
就是說我們要放棄了
lt says we quit.
那是你放棄了
lt says you quit!
誓詞是怎麼說的？
What about the oath?
那你告訴我
Tell me something, Ford.
一個死了的郵遞員又能投遞幾封信呢
How much mail can a dead postman deliver?
都結束了
lt's over.
那讓我去送信
Then l'll take it.
我信不過你
l can't trust you.
如果這就是結局...
lf this is the end...
如果這是最後一封投遞的信
...if this is the last piece of mail that ever gets delivered...
就讓我來發吧
...l'll take it.
無論誰發這封信，都有可能會犧牲
Whoever delivers this letter, Ford, probably dies for it.
我仍然還是個郵差！
l'm still a postman!
你欠我的
You owe it to me.
我也欠我自己的
l owe it to me.
那不能怪Ford
It's not Ford's fault.
他和你不一樣，他沒有你的那些經歷 他們都沒有
He's not like you. He doesn't have your memories. None of them do.
這就是他們的全部了
This is all they have.
-這是他們知道的唯一神聖的事 -什麼？
-lt's the only decent thing they know. -What?
做個郵差！
Being a postman?
都是胡扯，Abby
lt's all bullshit, Abby.
全是胡扯
All of it.
我穿制服只是為了保暖
l took the uniform off a skeleton to stay warm.
我只是安慰他們而已
l made up the rest to stay fed.
根本沒有所謂的...
There is no...
重建的美國
...Restored United States.
我覺得事情就是如此
l figured it was something like that.
我要去Saint Rose
l'm going to Saint Rose.
我帶你一起去
l'm taking you with me.
我已經幫你把馬準備好了
l've already packed your horse.
我知道你不想聽
l know you don't want to hear it...
但是你的腹中有我的孩子
...but that's my child inside you.
我想讓他出生在一個安全的地方
l want to see it born somewhere safe.
我想我認出你來了
l thought l recognized you.
Bethlehem將軍說當我把槍指著你時 你應該跪倒在地
General Bethlehem said you should be on your knees when l do this.
我才不理那個混蛋說些什麼
l don't give a damn what that asshole said.
將軍是個了不起的人物
The general is a great man!
將軍就他媽的是個瘋子
The general is a fucking lunatic.
你想見識一下什麼是男子漢？
You want to see a man?
那就是
That's a man.
準備好沒？
You ready?
好了
Yes.
你至少要比Bethlehem強些
You're a better man than Bethlehem.
我看得出來
l've seen it.
尊敬的Bethlehem
''To Bethlehem.
這是我的真心話
This letter is my testimony...
事實上並沒有
...to the fact that there is no...
重建後的美國
...Restored United States...
也沒有什麼郵政服務
...and there is no postal service.''
他想讓我相信這個？
He expects me to believe this?
這是真的
lt's true.
我當時就在那 他解散了郵遞員組織
l was there. He disbanded the carriers...
然後向西邊走了
...and rode west.
叛徒！
Traitor!
這麼說我贏了
Then l've won.
把我們昨天抓到的那個人帶過來 把他們一起處死
Bring the one we found yesterday. They can die together.
叛徒！ 你這個叛徒！
You traitor! You're a traitor!
那個人是那邊的二號人物
That one's the second-in-command.
怎麼沒讓我感到驚喜呢？
Why doesn't that surprise me?
我在想，長官...
l was thinking, sir...
對我們來說把他關起來也許更有價值
...he might be more valuable to us as a prisoner.
本打算讓你幹掉他的
You were supposed to kill him...
對嗎？
...weren't you?
但是我沒辦法靠近他
l couldn't get close enough.
你是誰？
Who are you?
我叫Clark
My name's Clark.
重建後的加州郵遞員
Postal Carrier for the Restored Republic of California.
你又是誰？
Who are you?
郵局局長，Ford
Postmaster Ford Lincoln Mercury.
萬分榮幸！
lt's an honor.
等一等
Wait!
等一等，先別開火
Wait a minute. Hold your fire.
你們倆並不認識？
You two don't know each other?
這將不會結束
This'll never be over.
會一直持續下去
lt'll go on.
除非我是在和一個該死的鬼魂在戰鬥
Except l'll be fighting a goddamn ghost.
-可以開槍了嗎？ -別開槍，該死的
-Should we fire, sir? -No, goddamn it!
我不會和鬼魂打仗
l won't fight a ghost.
Tabula...
...rasa...
...先生們
...gentlemen.
一段清白的歷史
A clean slate.
我要對所有的郵遞員窮追猛打
l want all mail carriers hunted down.
我一定要找到那個郵差
l want The Postman found.
我要狠狠地打擊他
l want him dealt with.
上校，集合部隊
Colonel, organize the scouts.
你說他往西走了？
You said he rode west?
而這是他的二號人物？
And this is his second-in-command?
是的，長官
Yes, sir!
我會留你一條命用來談判 要讓郵差投鼠忌器
l'll keep you to bargain with. The Postman is weak that way.
把槍扔到地上
Set your rifle on the ground!
扔到地上
Set it on the ground.
什麼？這個破玩意？
What? This old thing?
子彈都沒上上去呢
lt isn't even loaded.
我們這是在哪裡？
Where are we?
你們在大橋城
You're in Bridge City...
而這裡不允許槍支
...where we don't allow guns.
崗哨說你要來了
The sentry said you were coming.
我知道你，你...
l know you. You're...
...很出名
...famous.
曾經是...
l was once...
...有那麼...
...sort of...
一點點
...kind of.
不再是了
Not anymore.
你們要穿過去？
Looking to cross?
是的
We will be.
但現在我們想要一些吃的
Right now we'd appreciate some food.
沒問題
Okay.
在我們後面，還有幾個孩子
There are some kids behind us.
幾個？
How many?
3個
3.
3個，好吧
3. Okay.
進來吧，孩子們
Come on in, guys!
我知道你們就在那
l know you're out there.
-等等，等一等 -他想要什麼？
-Wait. Just wait. -What did he want?
請安靜，他說...
Hold on. He says...
...他在尋找郵差
...he's looking for The Postman.
再沒有這樣一回事了
There's no such thing anymore.
但那個騎馬的人說有這麼一回事
The man on the horse says there is.
他認為郵差就在這裡
He thinks he's here.
而他會帶著他的同夥再回來
And he's coming back with friends.
郵差時幹嗎的？
What's a postman?
你從來沒聽說過郵差？
You never heard of a postman?
你就是那個郵差？
Are you The Postman?
對
Yeah.
夥計，我聽說過你啊
l heard of you, man.
你很出名
You're famous.
也許，是吧
Yeah, l guess l am.
但突然之間 我已經...
And all of a sudden, l'm not...
...不再是個郵差了
...wearing the right clothes.
夥計，你會喜歡上這玩意的
Man, you're going to love this!
打開第二道瀑布
Open that second chute, bro!
郵差先生，你很有天賦
You have a gift, Postman.
在Pineview，我看見它又回來了
l saw it back in Pineview.
你給了我們都已經遺忘了的寶貴財富
You've given us all back what we'd forgotten.
你讓March覺得她彷彿重見光明
You made Mrs. March feel like she could see again.
你讓Ford覺得他就是這個世界的一分子
You made Ford feel like he was part of the world.
你給了我們希望...
You give out hope like it was...
...就像點亮你口袋裡的蠟燭
...candy in your pocket.
你還記得這個嗎？
Remember this?
我記得
l remember.
我常想，你是故意把這個留給我的
l always like to think that you left it on purpose.
這對我來說很不容易
This is hard for me.
Michael是我見過的最好的男人
Michael was the best man l ever knew.
我從來沒想過 我會像愛他那樣去愛另外一個人
l never thought there'd be another man l could love the way l loved him.
我沒法看得那麼遠
l couldn't see it for so long.
而你現在就要離開
And now you're leaving.
我害怕
And l'm afraid.
我害怕你再也找不到你的Saint Rose
l'm afraid you'll never find your Saint Rose.
這不重要
lt's not important.
我害怕你再也看不到你的小孩
l'm afraid you'll never see your baby.
我需要充足的電源！ 這個傢伙要走很遠的路呢！
l need full power, man! This dude's got a long way to go!
這機器運轉得真他媽的完美
This thing's working perfect, man!
比看起來還要高很多，不是嗎？
A lot higher than it looks, huh?
你差點就報銷了
You nearly went.
快進來吧
Get in.
在前面有三個規模很大的鎮子
There's 3 good-sized towns up ahead...
如果你能說服他們跟你走 你就能找到足夠的幫手
...with enough people to help you if you can convince them to come.
不要告訴任何人
Don't tell anybody...
說我喜歡玩這玩意，僅僅因為它好玩
...l like to ride this damn thing just for the hell of it.
你知道，作為一個領導 我得注意自身形象
Being a city official has its perks, you know?
相信我吧，夥計 這會讓你更快的
Trust me, man. This'll get you there a lot faster.
我怎麼停下來呢？
How do l stop?
別再這裡婆婆媽媽了
Quit worrying about the little things.
祝你好運，跑得飛快！
Good luck, and Godspeed.
長官，我向您報告！
Reporting for duty, sir!
-知道該怎麼做嗎？ -去說服人們
-Know what to do? -Talk to the people.
告訴他們這很重要
Tell them it's important.
告訴他們我們可以做到
Tell them we can make a difference.
再向前衝，親愛的朋友們 再向前衝
''Once more unto the breach, dear friends, once more...
...或者以死守衛我們的城牆
...or close the wall with our dead!
在和平時期，我們要謙虛彬彬有禮
In peace, nothing so becomes a man as modesty and humility.
但是一旦爆發戰爭
But when the blast of war blows in our ears...
我們就要像頭猛虎一樣勇猛
...then imitate the action of the tiger.
鼓起我們的勇氣 收起我們溫和的本性...
Summon up the blood. Disguise fair nature with rage...
去和敵人拚個你死我活
...and lend the eye a terrible aspect. ''
-他們是誰？ -不知道
-Who are they? -l don't know.
在我看來大部分都是老弱病殘
Looks like mostly women and young people to me.
有多少？
How many?
那是一支軍隊
lt's an army.
終於...
At last...
還是有人鼓起用來和我作戰了
...someone with courage enough to bring the fight to me.
先生們，算總賬的時候到了
Reckoning, gentlemen!
他們看起來熱血沸騰
They're an eager-looking bunch!
士氣真的是很重要
Morale is a dangerous thing.
把俘虜帶上來
Bring up the prisoner!
讓我們來告訴他們 遊戲該怎麼來玩
We'll show them how this game is played.
呆在這
Stay here.
他在投降？
ls he surrendering?
該死，我不希望這樣
God, l hope not.
小小搬運工
My little shipping clerk.
賣複印機的銷售員
Mr. copy-machine salesman.
我們倆是一對大騙子
We're both a couple of frauds.
說的沒錯
So be it.
但是一個偉人是由另一個偉人來成就的
But great men are made by other great men.
Rommel成就了Patton
Patton had Rommel.
Lee成就了Grant
Grant had Lee.
而你將會成就我的霸業
But l get you.
你不是將軍
You're no general.
你甚至也不是一個好的畫家
You're not even a good painter.
你想要激將我？
Trying to goad me into a fight?
如果戰爭由發起它的人來結束，就非常完美
lt'd be great if wars were fought just by the assholes who started them.
我們可以對這場戰爭作個了結
We could settle this right here...
只有你跟我
...you and me.
不幸的是，這種方法行不通
Unfortunately, it doesn't work that way.
但是在你的部隊裡卻可以
But it does in your army.
我引用八大法律中的...
l invoke Law Seven...
...第七條
...of the Laws of Eight!
在部隊裡誰都可以挑戰老大的位子
''Any man may challenge for leadership of the clan!''
我向你挑戰
l challenge you.
你不是我們一夥的，你沒有這個權力
You're not a Holnist. You're not a member. You don't have the right.
我擁有所有的權力
l have every right!
我引用第七條法律
l invoke Law Seven.
你去哪...?
Where...?
我要挑戰...
l challenge...
...老大的位子
...for leadership of the clan!
我在哪裡見過你？
Where do l know you from?
你下令搶劫...
''Cry havoc...
...然後餵養這些戰爭走狗
...and let slip the dogs of war!''
你還記得那些嗎？
You remember that?
莎士比亞
Shakespeare.
那個不想打仗的人
The one who didn't want to fight.
那時我就應該設法殺死你 但你看起來太強大
l should have found a way to kill you then, but you seemed so strong.
第七條法律...
Law Seven...
...那就是
...it is!
這場戰爭將在這裡作個了結
This war is settled here!
我研究過人們
l studied people.
我知道你的問題在哪
l know your problem.
你知道...
Do you know...
為什麼你不能打嗎？
...why you can't fight?
因為你不知道為何而戰
Because you have nothing to fight for.
你什麼也不關心
You don't care about anything.
你什麼也不在乎
You don't value anything.
你對什麼都不信任
You don't believe in anything!
而那些卻讓我變得更厲害
And that's what makes me better.
我信任...
l believe...
...美國
...in the United States.
我們本可以不這樣的
lt doesn't have to be this way.
我們本可以不用互相殘殺
We don't have to kill each other.
第三條法律...
''Law Three:
仁慈...
Mercy...
...是留給弱者的
...is for the weak.''
Ford，不要
Ford, don't!
第八條法律
''Law Eight:
只有一種懲罰...
There's only one penalty...
...而那就是死
...and that penalty is death.''
他不值得的
He isn't worth it.
現在我是部隊的頭兒
l'm the head of the clan now!
將會產生新的法律
There are going to be new laws!
第一條：
Law One:
不再殺戮
No more killing.
我們將擁有和平
There's going to be peace!
你覺得這樣如何？
How about it, Ford Lincoln Mercury?
Ford，要像個領袖的樣子
Be a leader, Ford.
第八條法律
Law Eight:
活著...
Live...
...就好好活
...and let live.
你爸爸寫信來說
Your daddy wrote to tell you...
他會盡快趕回來的
...he'll be here as soon as he can...
他非常愛你
...and that he loves you very much.
信件太慢了
Mail's slow.
我打算親自來告訴她
l'm going to have to see about that.
你的女兒
Your daughter.
她的名字叫希望
Her name is Hope.
我父親看到我們是如此的脆弱...
My father saw how fragile we are...
...如此輕易的就落入暴君的統治
...and how quickly we fell into the hands of tyranny.
他發現普通人...
He saw that ordinary men...
...也可以有潛力可挖，可以找到勇氣
...could reach deep within themselves and find courage.
他發現如果我們作為一個國家來溝通...
He saw that if we began to communicate as a nation...
...我們就可以再一次強大起來
...we could become strong again...
團結起來
...united.
但是他從來沒有真正見到過Saint Rose
But he never did see Saint Rose.
他說...
He said...
...還有太多的事情要去做
...there was too much to be done.
他許下承諾
He'd made a promise.
他信守承諾 追逐一個又一個的夢想
And in keeping it, he traded one dream for another.
無怨無悔
With no regrets.
所以，為了向我的父親表示敬意....
And so, in honor of my father....
那個小孩是我
That was me.
「郵差」 -=結束=-